Guide to the New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Commerce and Industry Association, 1873-1978
  - Subseries IV.5: Meeting Minutes, 1897-1973
    - Board of Directors
      - Vol. 21, 1934 February-1935 February (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 22, 1935 February-1936 March (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 23, 1936 April-1937 March (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 24, 1937 March-1938 March (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 25, 1938 April-1939 March (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 26, 1939 April-1940 March (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 27, 1940 April-1941 June (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 29, 1942 June-1943 December (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 30, 1944 January-1945 February (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 31, 1945 March-1946 January (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 32, 1946 February-1946 November (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 33, 1946 December--1948 January (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 34, 1948 February--1949 February (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 35, 1949 March-1950 January (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 36, 1950 February--1951 June (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 37, 1951 September-1952 February (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 38, 1952 March-1953 June (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 39, 1953 September-1954 December (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 40, 1955 January-1956 January (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 41, 1956 February-1957 February (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 42, 1957 March-1958 April (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 43, 1958 May-1959 April (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 44, 1959 May-1960 February (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 45, 1960 March-1961 April (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 46, 1961 May-1962 February (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 47, 1962 March-1963 February (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 48, 1963 March-1964 January (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 49, 1964 February-1964 November (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 50, 1964 December-1965 November (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 51, 1965 December-1966 November (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 52, 1966 December-1967 October (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 53, 1967 November-1968 September (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 54, 1968 October-1969 September (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 55, 1969 October-1970 September (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 56, 1970 October-1971 December (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 57, 1972 January-1973 January (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 58, 1973 February (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Board of Directors of the Merchants' Association, 1941-1972 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee
      - 1904 July-December (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - 1905 January-April (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - 1905 April-October (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - 1905 November-December (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - 1905 Index (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - 1906 January-June (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - 1906 July-December (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - 1906 Index (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - 1907 January-June (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - 1907 July-December (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - 1907 Index (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - 1908 January-December (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - 1908 Index (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - 1909 January-May (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - 1909 June-December (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - 1909 Index (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - 1910 January-June (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - 1910 July-December (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - 1910 Index (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - 1911 January-May (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - 1911 June-November (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - 1911 Index (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - 1912 January-April (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - 1912 May-December (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - 1912 Index (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - 1913 January-June (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - 1913 July-December (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - 1913 Index (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - 1914 January-May (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - 1914 June-December (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - 1914 Index (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - 1915 March-October (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - 1915 November-December (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - 1915 Index (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - 1916 January-May (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - 1916 June-December (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - 1916 Index (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - 1917 January-June (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - 1917 July-December (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - 1917 Index (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - 1918 January-April (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - 1918 July-December (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - 1918 Index (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - 1919 January-May (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - 1919 June-December (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - 1920 February-June (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - 1920 July-December (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - 1921 January-May (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - 1921 June-December (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - 1922 January-June (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - 1922 July-August (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - 1922 October-December (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - 1923 January-May (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - 1923 June-October (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - 1923 November-December (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - 1924 January-May (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - 1924 September-December (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - 1925 January-April (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - 1925 May-November (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - 1926 January-February (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - 1926 March-December (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - 1927 January-November (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - 1928 January (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - 1928 November-December (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - 1929 January-June (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - 1929 September (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - 1929 Index (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - 1930 January-December (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - 1931 February-December (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - 1932 February-October (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - 1933 March-July (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - 1933 September-October (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - 1933 Index (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - 1933-1938 Index (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - 1934 January-September (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - 1935 February-May (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - 1936 February-August (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - 1937 March-November (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - 1938 January-February (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - 1938 April-December (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - 1938-1942 Index (Box 129, Folder 13)
      - 1939 April-November (Box 129, Folder 14)
      - 1940 February-October (Box 129, Folder 15)
      - 1941 February-December (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - 1942 January-April (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - 1942 June-December (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - 1942-1946 Index (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - 1943 January-November (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - 1944 March-December (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - 1945 March-December (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - 1946 February-November (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - 1947 January-December (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - 1947-1951 Index (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - 1948 January-October (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - 1949 January-December (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - 1950 February-November (Box 130, Folder 13)
      - 1951 January-February (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - 1951 April-December (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - 1951-1953 Index (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - 1952 January-December (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - 1953 January-July (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - 1953 August-December (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - 1953-1956 Index (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - 1954 January-December (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - 1955 January-October (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - 1956 January-March (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - 1956 April-December (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - 1956-1959 Index (Box 131, Folder 12)
      - 1957 January-September (Box 131, Folder 13)
      - 1958 January-December (Box 131, Folder 14)
      - 1959 January-December (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - 1959-1962 Index (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - 1960 January-December (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - 1961 February-December (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - 1962 February-September (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - 1963 January-October (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - 1964 February-November (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - 1965 February-December (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - 1966 January-November (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - 1967 February (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - 1968 March-December (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - 1969 January-December (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - 1970 March-December (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - 1971 January-December (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - 1972 February-November (Box 132, Folder 14)
      - 1973 January-February (Box 132, Folder 15)
      - Executive Sessions of the Executive Committee and Board of Directors of the Merchants Association of New York/Commerce and Industry Association of New York, 1963-1971 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Member Meetings
      - 1897 June-1907 March (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - 1907 November-1915 March (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - 1916 May-1929 May (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - 1930 May-1940 June (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - 1941 May-1958 May (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - 1942-1972 Annual Members Meetings (Box 194, Folder 5)
      - 1959 April-1968 March (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - 1969 January-1973 January (Special Meetings and Annual Meetings) (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Member's Council
      - 1913 October-1926 December (Box 193, Folder 3)
      - 1927 February-1928 May (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - 1928 December-1930 September (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - 1930 October-1933 July (Box 194, Folder 1)
      - 1933 November-1935 December (Box 194, Folder 2)
      - 1936 March-1940 February (Box 194, Folder 3)
      - 1940 October-1942 February (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Luncheon Meeting--Radio, 1925 (Box 374, Folder 9)
  - Subseries IV.6: Printed Materials, 1873-1973
    This small subseries contains an assortment of pamphlets, booklets, and compilations of reports, mostly originating from the first half of the 20th century. Materials focus on topics of both local and national concern, such as transportation, communication, and city development. Items are organized according to their subject matter or title. For the Commerce and Industry Association's more formal publications that were intended for wider distribution, researchers should consult the New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry Publications collection.
    - By-laws, 1943-1949 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - Civil Defense, 1951 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - Commercial Interests
      - International, 1916-1957 (Box 340, Folder 1)
      - New York City
        - 1912-1915 (Box 340, Folder 2)
        - 1919-1939 (Box 340, Folder 3)
        - 1942-1955 (Box 340, Folder 4)
      - United States
        - 1878-1916 (Box 340, Folder 5)
        - 1941-1948 (Box 340, Folder 6)
        - Cost of Condemnation Proceedings and Analysis of References, 1903 (bound volume) (Box 460)
        - Interstate Commerce Commission in the Matter of Differential Inland Freight Rates to and from North Atlantic Ports, 1905 (bound volume) (Box 461)
    - Legislation, 1873-1949 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - The Merchants’ Association of New York Transactions
      - 1897-1900 (Box 368)
      - 1901-1902 (Box 370)
      - 1903-1904 (Box 360)
      - 1905-1906 (Box 362)
      - 1907 (Box 359)
    - National Defense, 1914-1941 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - New York City--Development and Improvement
      - 1901-1906 (Box 341, Folder 2)
      - 1901-1939 (Box 341, Folder 3)
      - City Expenses--Reports, 1898-1903 (bound volume) (Box 459)
    - New York City--Promotional Material, 1906-1973 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - New York State
      - 1931-1940 (Box 341, Folder 5)
      - 1945-1966 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - Organization, 1899-1905 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlet of Economic Questions, 1897-1901 (Box 358)
    - Port of New York, 1913-1941 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Post-War Planning Committee, 1943-1945 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Public Notices, 1898-1909 (2 Folders) (Box 377, Folder 3-4)
    - Tariffs and Customs, 1906-1941 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - Trade Pamphlets, 1897-1898 (Box 364)
    - Transactions--Express Cases, 1897-1901 (Box 366)
- Series V: Committee on Arbitration, 1820s-1973
  The Committee on Arbitration was a significant body of the Chamber of Commerce, although its importance varied greatly throughout the Chamber's existence. Because the Committee retained such a large portion of its records, it was designated as its own series, Series V, apart from the Subseries VI.2: General Committees. Established during the formative years of the Chamber, the Committee on Arbitration was appointed to hear and rule on disputes on mercantile and marine matters. The Committee on Arbitration was instrumental in securing legislation to create a Court of Arbitration, and was widely recognized for its role in developing arbitration systems in commercial and civic associations nationwide. Series V is divided into three subseries according to the original order of the material.
  - Subseries V.1: Arbitration Cases, 1820s-1973
    The bulk of the series is found in Subseries 1 which consists of arbitration case records submitted to the Chamber’s Committee on Arbitration. The Committee on Arbitration did not keep original documents for early arbitration cases; instead they recorded the name of the disputants, a brief description of the case, and the names and decision of the arbitrators’ in their Committee minute books. Although this collection does not contain the original copies of the Committee minute books from that time period, the cases were compiled into a publication entitled, Earliest Arbitration Records of the Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York, Committee Minutes, 1779-1792, which can be found in the holdings of Columbia University Libraries. The Committee on Arbitration began keeping original materials in the 1820s and while case records are inconsistent, most files found here contain correspondence and/or official arbitration documents. Following the renewal of the Committee on Arbitration in 1912, case records are more comprehensive and standardized; they often include the stenographer’s minutes of the proceedings and, in some instances, evidence.
    - Cases and Correspondence, 1820s (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Cases and Correspondence, 1820s-1850s, (3 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Cases and Correspondence, 1830s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cases and Correspondence, 1840 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Cases and Correspondence, 1850s (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1824--Phelps, Thadeus and Verdine Elsworth v. Andrew Kerr (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - 1845--Steamship Massachusetts v. Theodore Maurice (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1848--Schuchardt and Gebbard v. Benjamin Blossom (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1860--Maitland, Phelps and Co. v. Bank Whistling Wind (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - 1862
      - Cokino and Co. v. E. Cunard (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Reeve, Case and Banks v. Market Bank (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 1863
      - Boonen, Graves and Co. v. Sturges, Bennet and Co. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - H. Sautter and Wierum v. P. Seymour Henway (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - J. Patrick and Co. v. W. Scott and Son (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - W. Roper and Co. v. Place and Wilson (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 1864
      - Application of Whitlock (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Cunard, E. v. Bruce and Cook (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Dabuey, C.W. v. Ship Carolus Magnus and Captain Ashley (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Everett and Co. v. Rowland and Aspinwall (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Storm Smith and Co. v. Burger, Hurlbut and Livingston (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Wylie and Wade v. Pavenstedt and Co. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 1865
      - Hayden, Heywood v. Zimmerman Faris and Co. (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - J. Hess and Co. v. Edward Cunard (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Pardo Seixas and Co. v. Wright, Gillies and Brother (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - 1866--Breithaupt and Wilson v. Hoadley, Eno and Co. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1867
      - Beards and Cummings v. Maitland, Phelps and Co. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - W. Hunter and Co. v. Law, Young and Co. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1868--Application of L. Marx (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1874
      - Gardener, George A. v. Laffin and Rand Powder Co. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - H. Becker and Co. v. General Insurance Company of Dresden (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - V.W. McFarlane and Co. v. Randolph and Charles Degenes (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Thebaud v. Albert Cobb (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Wood, Payson and Colgate v. C. Menelas (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 1875
      - Archer and Bull v. George W. Dow and Sons (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Brown, Ephraim D. v. Thomas Patten (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Bryant, William C. v. George Hawthorne (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Bryant, William C. v. George Hawthorne (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Busk, Joseph, Et Al. v. Edmund Pavenstedt, Et Al. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Couisinery and Co. v. Wilkins and Co (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Holtz v. Renauld, Francois and Co. (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Hooker and Co. v. Isaac Jenks (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Lake, Mary E. and Eliza C. Doyle v. Francis Holbrook (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Lichtenberg, Charles v. Kunhardt and Co. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Roosevelt, Mary and James v. Sullivan (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Sinclair and Milne v. Eli Charlier (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - 1876
      - Boyd, James v. William Knoepfel (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Crowell, Gorham v. Franklin Woodruff, Et Al. (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Delemater, Cornelius and George Robinson v. George C. Martin (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Fickett, E.C. v. Royal Phelps, Et Al. (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Huntington, E.H.M. v. Warren Beebe and Co. (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Inhorst, Henrich v. Joseph Bensusan (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Inhorst, Henrich v. Joseph Bensusan, (2 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      - Jewell, Harrison, and Co. v. Dentz, Mestre and Co. (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Lewisohn Brothers v. Stewart Brothers (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Marcus Hunter and Co. v. A.H. Solomon (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - R.G. Mitchell and Co. v. Henry Marquardt (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - 1877
      - A.H. Solomon and Co. v. George Palen and Co. (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Bauendahl and Co. v. Ferdinand Mayer and Co. (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Giles, William O. v. Edward Simon and Others, (4 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
      - J.H. Winchester and Co. v. Galway and Casado (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Jones, B.H., Et Al. v. Edward Matthews, (2 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
      - Kirkland, John v. Sarah Barney Sturges (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Mayer and Co. v. Pastor, Walkinshaw and Co., (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 13-14)
      - Oakes, Edward v. John L. Howard (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Phelps, Dodge and Co. v. Great Western Steamship Line (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Schooner Willow Harp v. The Steamer Leopard, (3 Folders) (Box 325, Folder 1-3)
      - Schooner Willow Harp v. The Steamer Leopard--Evidence (Box 375)
      - Warner, DeForest and Co. v. Titus Sheard and Edward Burns (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - White, J.J. v. Lane and Son (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - 1878
      - Balen, Peter, Et Al. v. Carl Ricknagel, Et Al. (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - C.H. Mallory and Co. v. Murray, Ferris and Co. (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Havemeyer, Et Al. v. Alexandre, Et Al. (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - James B. Grosvenor and Co. v. Henry Newman (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Lanman and Kemp v. Kraus and Stetten (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Ralli and Brothers v. Thomas E. Proctor (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Ward and Co. v. Clarke and Co. (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Wright and Co. v. Hartford Wool Co. (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Wright and Co. (Steamship Geddo) v. Munzinger and Pitzipio (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - 1879
      - Buckley, G.P. v. S. and W. Welsh (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Erie Railway Company v. Inman Steamship Co. (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Gallup, Albert S. v. John P. Kennedy and Cornelius K. Garrison (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Gallup, Albert S. v. John P. Kennedy and Cornelius K. Garrison, (2 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
      - Lewis, Stark W. v. Emelio Puig (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Porter, Elihu v. Lyons and Bunns (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Porter, Elihu v. Lyons and Bunns (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Potts and Son v. Wheeler and Co. (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Wilson and Co. v. M.C. de Markoe (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1880
      - Archer, George E. v. The Receiver of the Central Rail Roads of New Jersey (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - H.H. Swift and Co. v. Wilkinson Brothers and Co. (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Phelps, Dodge, and Co. v. S.S. Bristol (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Torrey, William A. v. Thom McFarlane (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Wakefield, Cyrus v. Wood, Payson and Colgate (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Watson, George S. v. Thomas Henderson (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Welsh, S. and W. v. Havemeyer and Elder (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1881
      - Cohn, Lazarus and Co. v. The Bark Nordkyn and Owners (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Darrell and Co. v. Nix and Co. (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Evans, George v. E.S. Wheeler (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Rose, McAlpine and Co. v. National Steamship Co. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1882
      - George A. Alden and Co. v. H.K. and F.B. Thurber and Co. (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Gualterio de Vera Carril v. Enrique Crespo (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Leaycraft, Charles R. v. Robert A. Robertson (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Purcell, James (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1883
      - The China and Japan Trading Company v. George G. Moore and Others (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Halsey, James v. Julia Tallmadge and Laura F. Field (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Mott, Samuel D. v. J.P. Billups and Co. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 1884-- Gardner, Oliver L. v. Henry W. Knight (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 1885
      - Cutter, John D. v. Edward P. Cutter (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Semon Bache and Co. v. The British and Foreign Marine Insurance Company (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 1888
      - Cort, Nicholas L. v. Excelsior Manufacturing Co. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Hydrogen Company of the United States v. Charles W. Whitney (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 1889
      - Arnoux, William H. v. E. Harrison Sanford (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Keen and Coates v. British and Foreign Insurance Company (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - N.M. Lake Erie and Water Rail Road v. Central Rail Road Co. of New Jersey (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 1890--C.V. Pustau and Co. v. McKesson and Robbins (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1894-- Talcott, James v. The Canton Mills Company (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 1895
      - Anrich, Emmanuel L. v. The Mercantile Credit Guarantee Company of New York (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Lisbon Falls Fibre Co. v. John Monroe and Wallace Muller (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 1896--McKesson and Robbins v. G. Gulbenkian and Co. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1912
      - F.S. Ellenberg and Co. v. Theo. Tiedemann and Sons (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Guggenheimer, Samuel H. v. Herman Heidelberg (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - H and R Johnson v. Traitel Marble Co. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - W. E. Byles and Co., Ltd. v. William H. Stiles (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Wills and Marvin Co. v. Federal Terra Cotta Co. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 1913
      - Blanchard, Isaac H. v. George M. Jacques (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Foundation Co. v. Heddon Construction Co. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Fried, Mendelson and Co. v. Herman Wolfert (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Henry Kupfer and Co. v. M. Brukenfeld (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - The Raw Products Co. v. L. Littlejohn and Co. (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Rosenfeld, Francis M. v. Max Tahl (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - White Weld and Co. v. James Ottley (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - W.R. Grace and Co. v. L. Littlejohn and Co. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - 1914
      - Alexander and Baldwin, Ltd. v. The Males Co. (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Everett, Heaney and Co. v. Clarence Whitman and Co., Inc. (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Greer, Benjamin W. v. W.H. Duval and Co. (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Henry Kruper and Co. v. Joseph Mistal (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Mill, Ernest H. v. United Dressed Beef Co. (Box 36, Folder 3)